Hey, judges. I'm Layken.
I'm from Louisiana, and I've been hearing
about these big data centers
and SpaceX launch facilities proposed
around the state.
I wanted to read more about this and found
it hard to find sources that
I could trust. So I built Public Parish.
This is a free, open-source, nonpartisan
tool for keeping track of
Louisiana government decisions.
I'd like to show the Meta $50 billion data
center project.
Here on this page, we bring together what
the established record is.
As well as the timeline of the project.
Everything here is built and generated on
top of official
source documentation from councils,
commissions, organizations related
to this project.
Everything stated here has citations.
We can open these, read the official
source or even link back to
the PDFs put out by the Louisiana Public
Service Commission.
Another cool thing we can do is ask about
this story.
So if we go here and we ask a question,
what happens if Meta ends its
service agreement early?
So what happens is our system is looking
at all the official
documentation in our database, searching
through them what is relevant
to your question, picking out the answer
and writing it for you.
And again, everything here, this gives us
an explanation and it's cited.
So we're able to open up the source and
verify the claims in this
answer. Another thing we can do with this
project is follow it through email.
So any material updates that come out
related to the Meta data center
will be sent to you as an update through
email.
Here's an update that I received recently.
Cool thing here is you can reply to the
email and this uses the same
functionality as the chat inside the
application and Public Parish
replies with the explanation as well as
the cited sources
to verify the claim.
We're launching today with support for
statewide stories as well as
three parishes here in Louisiana.
Users can select their home parish and
keep up with anything happening locally.
View issues, ask questions, and follow
anything here through email.
For the hackathon sponsors, Convex handles
our database authentication
and workflows. Firecrawl is for scraping
and monitoring
all of the official sources and documents.
OpenAI handles the reasoning, extraction,
and answers questions through the Convex
AI Gateway and AgentMail
handles everything from sending out update
emails as well as handling
the replies to user questions in email.
This is live today at publicparish.com.